myputlocker.me 2018-06-04

# PRIVACY POLICY - PutLocker Free

We at Beetv are aware of how much you care for the personal information you use and share. , and we appreciate your trust that we will handle it with care and sensibility. We assure you that we do not collect personal information from you unless you provide it to us and will never provide or sell personal information to entities that are outside of the BeeTV community.  
By visiting BeeTV, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

****Information Collected****  
We gather personal information, such as names, email addresses, and so on., when willfully presented by our guests. The data you give is utilized to satisfy your particular request, unless you provide for us consent to utilize it as a part of an alternate way, for instance, to add you to one of our mailing records.

**Cookies and Web Beacon**  
Our site may utilize cookies and/or any web beacon which are valuable for gathering data, for example, program sort and working framework, following the quantity of guests to the site, and seeing how guests utilize the Site.  
Individual data can’t be gathered through cookies and other web beacon, however, if you provided the personal information beforehand, cookies may be fixed to such data. Third parties, for example, our promoters might likewise cookies treats to gather data as a part of the course of serving advertisements to you. Most web programs consequently acknowledge cookies, however you can normally alter your browser settings to decline cookies based on your preference. 

**Distribution of Information**  
We will never share any of your personal information to any third party for promoting purposes. However, we may impart data to legislative organizations and agencies or different organizations supporting us in extortion aversion or examination. We may do so when either allowed or needed by law; attempting to ensure against or counteract real or potential extortion or unapproved exchanges; or, exploring misrepresentation which has effectively occurred.

**Our Commitment to Data Security**  
Your personal data and information’s will be kept secured. Only approved staff of this site (who have consented to keep data secure and classified) have admittance to this data. All messages and pamphlets from this site permit you to withdraw of further mailings.

**How to Contact Us**  
If you have any questions or concerns about the BeeTv Privacy Policy or its implementation you may contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

**Updates & Effective Date**  
We may update this privacy notice from time to time. We will notify you about material changes in the way we treat personal information by placing a notice on our site.  
A notice will be placed on our site to notify you for any changes we made to the BeetV Privacy Policy

We urge you to occasionally inquire and survey this arrangement so you generally will realize what data we gather, how we utilize it, and to whom we reveal it.

© Copyright 2017 MyPutLocker.me - All Rights Reserved.
